<Document>
# Chaplain

You are the custodian of the station's chapel, as well as a performer of small miracles through use of a unique sanctified implement.

## Sanctified Item
Upon arrival at the station, you'll be able to use a special action on any item in the world to make it [bold]sanctified.[/bold] This will imbue it with special properties, and will also designate the specific type of item chosen as your [bold]sanctified archetype.[/bold]

If your sanctified item is ever destroyed, you will regain the ability to sanctify an item, with one important caveat: [red]You will only be able to sanctify items of the [bold]EXACT SAME kind[/bold] as your sanctified archetype![/red]

For example, if you were to sanctify a flashlight and had it destroyed, you would not be allowed to sanctify a different kind of flashlight, such as ones with different colors or seclites.

<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ChoppingAxe" Caption=""/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingHeadHatWitch" Caption=""/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Lantern" Caption=""/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingHandsGlovesColorWhite" Caption=""/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Wrench" Caption=""/>
</Box>
Every single item in the game can be sanctified! Pick one that suits your character's beliefs best, or just something that you think might make for interesting roleplay!

## Chaplain Powers
### Blessed Healing
While holding or wearing your sanctified item, you can [yellow]heal small amounts of Brute and Burn damage from a target.[/yellow]

### Summon Familiar
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobBatRemilia" Caption=""/>
</Box>
While holding or wearing your sanctified item, you can [yellow]summon Remilia, a loyal bat companion[/yellow] who will follow your instructions and help any way she can.

Using this action creates a ghost role that must be taken in order for Remilia to be summoned, so response times to the action may vary.

### Holy Water
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="DrinkHolyWaterFull" Caption=""/>
</Box>
By interacting with any container of water using your sanctified item in hand, you can create holy water, which has [yellow]minor healing properties[/yellow] when drank by any creature. You can see its full effects here:

<GuideReagentEmbed Reagent="Holywater" Caption=""/>

### Holy Damage
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobRevenant" Caption=""/>
</Box>
Holy damage is a special damage type that all sanctified items become capable of dealing. Holy damage [yellow]only damages very specific kinds of creatures,[/yellow] all of whom you won't see during standard gameplay.
</Document>
